Right now, we're facing a man-made
disaster of global
scale, our greatest threat in
thousands of years, climate
change.
If we don't take action, the collapse
of our civilizations and the
extinction of much of the natural world
is on the horizon.
The world's people have spoken.
Their message is clear.
Time is running out.
The amount of carbon dioxide in the
atmosphere now is 50% higher
than it was in 1900. And not
only are we piling in more and more
carbon dioxide in the atmosphere. But we
are chopping down the forests of the
earth at a great rate. And the forests
themselves are the most efficient
consumers of carbon dioxide than
there are on earth. We're going to
destroy the ground because the soil
of a rainforest isn't very good. We are
actually tampering with the climate of
the earth and with the very atmosphere
that we breathe. When we
talk about the disappearance of the ozone
layer,We don't know what will
happen when the ozone layer goes.
The world has become so fragile
that we cannot subject the earth to the
tortures we can now inflict upon it.
When we talk about the greenhouse effect,
we're talking about something that
affects the entire earth.
And these problems are life and death
problems. They go to the root of the
viability of the planet itself.
See, if there's one thing that is
biologically certain about
the human species is that it is a
human species, one
species. If we
don't stop the destruction of our natural
world, nothing else will matter.
Simply put, if we don't protect
nature, we can't protect
ourselves.
The only way we can solve a problem
is by a human solution.
Never can we sit back and wait for
miracles to save us. Miracles
don't happen. Sweat happens.
Efforts happens. Thought
happens.